(Howard:)All right, this is an exact duplicate
of the Wolowitz Zero-Gravity...
(Howard:)...Human Waste Disposal System
as deployed on the Space Station.
(Raj:)Don't you mean the Wolowitz Zero-Gravity
Human Waste Distribution System?
Good one, yeah.
[FAKES LAUGH]
(Howard:)It's hilarious. Now.
(Howard:)Here's an approximation of the spare parts
available on the space station.
(Howard:)We gotta find a way, using nothing but this,
to reinforce this.
So the waste material avoids the turbine.
(Raj:)You mean, so it doesn't hit the fan?
You know, I have to say I thought the toilet
humor would get less funny with repetition.
(Sheldon:)Apparently, there is no law of diminishing
comedic returns with space poop.
[KNOCKING]
(Stuart:)- Hey, Leonard.
- Hey, Stuart.
- You busy?
- Uh...
(Howard:)Classified, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Yeah, it's a regular Manhattan Project.